AUDREY THOMASSON

UI/UX DESIGNER & FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a UI/UX Designer and Front-End Developer. After earning a degree in graphic design, I have designed ads for a magazine publisher, managed at a 5-star resort balancing people and business interests, and freelanced as a real estate photographer shooting and listing properties. My work experience allows me to bring a greater depth of knowledge to a product development team. By understanding the user – I am ready to help your team turn the complex into simple, beautiful user experiences.

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX DESIGNER & FRONT-END DEVELOPER (APPRENTICESHIP)

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL: AUGUST 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

- Intensive full-time six-month bootcamp focusing on front-end development, UI/UX fundamentals, problem-solving and working in a remote team environment
- · Built single page apps individually and by teams with full CRUD functionality
- · Main technologies covered: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, JSON, Node.js, Git, and GitHub

REAL ESTATE PHOTOGRAPHER & MARKETING MANAGER

FREELANCE- NASHVILLE, TN: 2010 - 2020

- · Photograph and film real estate for MLS listings primarily with a large Keller Williams group
- · Documented property specs and researched property information
- · Listed properties on MLS and wrote marketing information

ASSISTANT MARKETING MANAGER

JOYMOVES PILATES STUDIO- AUSTIN, TX: 2007 - 2010

- · Design marketing materials including online content, direct mail pieces, business cards, ads
- · Photograph pilates studio and pilates poses for use in print and online
- Insure accuracy of billing in MindBody Online Scheduling Software
- · Interview potential job candidates and train new hires

SPA SUPERVISOR

LAKE AUSTIN SPA RESORT- AUSTIN, TX: 2004 - 2007

- Responsible for daily operation of 25,000 sq ft luxury spa facility with a staff of over 130
- Provide customer service to a high-end clientele to maintain five star service reputation
- · Hire and train coordinators and locker room attendants
- · Monitor and insure accuracy of all billing procedures for spa and resort guests

DESIGNER / PRODUCTION MANAGER

UNITED PARENTING PUBLICATIONS- DALLAS, TX: 2001 - 2003

- · Designed classified ads and page layouts for 22 unique monthly parenting magazines
- · Organized workflow for production department and tracked status of all ads in production
- · Coordinated ad creation and changes with sales staff in home office as well as other states
- · Insured accuracy of all ads, layouts, and files transmitted to printing facility
- · Adhered to strict printing schedule while meeting all deadlines

Contact



615.200.8357



audreyuxdev@gmail.com



github.com/audreythomasson linkedin.com/in/audrey-thomasson



audreythomasson.github.io

Tools & Technology

HTML5

CSS3 / Sass

Javascript

React & Vue

Visual Studio Code

NPM

JSON Server

Figma

FireBase

Bootstrap / Semantic UI / Material UI

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Git & GitHub version control

Command line work flow

Skills

User Testing / Usability Testing
User Personas

Wireframes & Journey Mapping

Interactive Prototypes / Mockups

Remote Teamwork

Education

UI/UX Design & Front-End Development

Nashville Software School Aug 2020 - Feb 2021

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS
Graphic Design, Cum Laude

Texas State University